jaypeeonline.net 2017-01-13

# Policies - JaypeeOnline

## PRIVACY POLICY

**Automatically-Recorded Information**

**JaypeeOnline** (“the Site” or “JaypeeOnline”) records your IP address for the purpose of diagnosing potential problems with the hosting service, as well as to administer the Site. It is also used to help determine the number of unique vistors to, and page views of, the Site.

**Cookie/Tracking Technology**  
JaypeeOnline uses cookies to save an encrypted version of your account password so you won’t have to re-enter it as you surf through the Site. Your login cookie will expire immediately upon clicking the logout link.  
Advertisers

We use various online advertising services to display ads on the Site. These ads may contain cookies. While cookies are used in other parts of the Site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by the ad company concerned, and we do not have access to this information.

Currently, we serve advertisements from the following:

* Google Adsense  
* HelloToken  
* MaxCDN

Third parties such as our advertisers may also use cookies to serve ads to you based on your visit to our site and other sites on the internet. If you want to opt out of our third-party advertiser (Google Adsense)’s use of cookies, please visit the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Registration Forms**  
The Site’s registration forms require users to provide basic contact information including names and email addresses. General demographic information including zip codes, age, etc. may also be requested. This information is not verified and may be changed by site users at any time.

Email addresses provided with the Site’s registration forms are used to get in touch with registered users when necessary to remind them of their password, lapses in login or pending account termination. Your email address will never be used for any other purpose nor will it be divulged to any third party.

Demographic and profile data may also be collected at the Site. This information is shared with advertisers only on an aggregate basis and will never be used in any other fashion.

**Online Applications**  
The Site’s registered users may have the ability to participate in surveys, polls and other interactive applications. Information submitted to these will not be provided to any third party.

**External Links**  
The Site may contain links to other Web sites. JaypeeOnline is not responsible, and may not be held liable, for the privacy policies, privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Public Forums**  
JaypeeOnline allows registered and anonymous users to participate in discussions within the Site, especially via the blog commenting system. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in this and other public areas, including but not limited to message forums, become public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. We may not be held liable for any harm resulting in your own disclosure of your personal information via the Site.

**Security**  
The Site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of information under our control. While measures are in place, please be aware that nothing is 100% secure and we do not claim it to be so.

**Data Quality/Access**  
To change or modify any personal account information provided during site registration, you may visit the following URL: https://jaypeeonline.net/wp-admin/profile.php.

**Contacting Us**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, our practices, or regarding your activities within this Web site, you can contact us via the [Contact page](https://jaypeeonline.net/contact/).

## COMMENT POLICY

JaypeeOnline welcomes any type of comments that are: supportive, dissenting, critical or inquisitive.

Comments that are abusive, off-topic, attacks someone’s reputation, promotes hatred or hostility of any kind, contains foul language or outright spam will be DELETED.

All comments that contain SEO keywords will not be marked as spam but will be DELETED.

All comments are moderated and have to be approved by the editor before being published.

All comments are scanned and filtered by **Akismet**. It does a great job of filtering spam but the technology is not perfect and at times, may flag legitimate comments as spam due to false positives. If your comment doesn’t show up within 24-48 hours and you think that your comment was inadvertently flagged as spam please let us know via the [Contact page](https://jaypeeonline.net/contact/).

## DISCLOSURE POLICY

**This policy is valid from January 1, 2007**

This blog is a personal blog written and edited by me. This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation.

This blog abides by word of mouth marketing standards. We believe in honesty of relationship, opinion and identity. The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post will be clearly identified as paid or sponsored content.

The owner(s) of this blog is compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though the owner(s) of this blog receives compensation for our posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers’ own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

This blog does contain content which might present a conflict of interest. This content will always be identified.
